asp-software.org 2018-10-03

# Privacy Statement of the Association of Software Professionals | Association of Software Professionals

**The web sites and services covered by this Policy**  
We currently operate the following web sites (the "Sites"): 

  * www.asp-software.org 
  * members.asp.software.org 
  * www.asp-software.com 
  * downloads.asp-software.com 
  * www.isvcon.org 

In addition, we own other domain names (e.g. www.asp-shareware.org ) that may redirect to the home page of the Association of Software Professionals and/or content-specific "subsites" of the ASP.   
From time to time, we may add new sites that may not be listed above, but they will provide a link to this Privacy statement and will be governed by its terms. 

**Information Logged Automatically**  
The ASP maintains web logs to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. This information is primarily used to track page traffic, search phrases used to find our site, and browsers or operating systems used so we can better serve our visitors. This information is not made public. 

**Information on Cookies**  
ASP web sites may contain "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data that is sent to your browser, which will store the cookie on your computer if your browser is enabled to accept cookies. 

The ASP uses cookies to customize your experience with our sites and services. Personal information collected through the use of these technologies will be handled according to this Policy. 

Most internet browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to your browser instructions or "Help" screen to learn more about how to manage cookies. Please note, however, that if you block cookies, some portions of the ASP web sites and services may not function properly. 

**Links to External Sites**  
This site contains links to other sites. The Association of Software Professionals is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

**Newsgroups**  
This site makes both public and private newsgroups available to its visitors and members. Although the ASP has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control, please keep in mind that any information that is disclosed in these areas may still become public. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**  
This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Application Information**  
Membership application information is collected using an SSL-enabled secure server. In order to obtain membership with the ASP we require that you provide us with:   
First and Last Names, Street Address, City, State or Province (required for US and Canada), Country, Email Address, and Phone Number   
Additional information that may be requested to expedite membership approval but is not required are:   
Company Name, Public Phone Number, Public Fax Number, Public Email Address, Website Address, and Company or Product Description 

**Opt-out, Reviewing and Changing Personal Data**  
Our site provides members the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request membership information.   
Members can review or change their membership and opt-out information by going to the members only area and selecting the [Change my information](https://members.asp-software.org/updatemember1.asp) link. 

**Credit Card Information**  
The ASP does not disclose credit card account information provided by its members. When members choose to pay using their credit cards, the ASP submits the information needed to obtain payment to the appropriate services. 

**Sharing Information**  
The ASP is committed to protecting your privacy. We will not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose or share your email address or any other personal information to any third party without first obtaining your explicit consent. 

**Contact Information**  
If you have questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our web sites, please feel free to contact the ASP using the information provided on our [Contact](https://www.asp-software.org/www/asp/contact-us/) page. 

**Consumer Rights Information**  
California Civil Code Section 1789.3  
Pricing information is provided as part of the membership sign-up page(s) for this site.   
Contact information can be found in the Contact Information section preceding this section.   
Complaints. The Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the Department of Consumer Affairs may be contacted in writing at 1020 N. Street, #501, Sacramento, CA 95814, or by telephone at 1-916-445-1254. 

**Notice of changes to the Policy**  
The ASP reserves the right to change this Policy at any time by notifying members via newsgroup post of the existence of a new Policy and/or posting the new Policy on the ASP sites. All changes to the Policy will be effective when posted, and your continued use of any ASP site or service after the posting will constitute your acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.
